<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tv_shows on First-Gear.be</title>
    <link>/tv_shows/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tv_shows on First-Gear.be</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tv_shows/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Ages of Rock</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/7_ages_of_rock/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/7_ages_of_rock/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: A definitive landmark series charting the emergence and re-emergence of rock music as a global force, told through the musicians who have shaped this most enduring of genres.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aladdin</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/aladdin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/aladdin/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: In &amp;ldquo;Aladdin: The Series&amp;rdquo; - Aladdin, the clever hero of Agrabah, continues his adventures with the help of his fiancee Princess Jasmine, his pet monkey Abu, Magic Carpet, Iago the greedy parrot, and of course his best friend the semi-cosmic Genie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archer (2009)</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/archer_2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/archer_2009/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Archer follows the exploits of eight dysfunctional secret agents of the International Secret Intelligence Service (ISIS), a fictional New York-based intelligence agency. They are : Sterling Archer, the show&amp;rsquo;s narcissistic, womanizing protagonist, Malory Archer, ISIS director and Sterling&amp;rsquo;s snarky, emotionally distant mother, Lana Kane, Sterling&amp;rsquo;s love interest and mother of his infant daughter, and by far the most professional field agent at ISIS, Ray Gillette, the agency&amp;rsquo;s openly gay bomb specialist, Pam Poovey, the head of the agency&amp;rsquo;s Human Resources department who is often ridiculed by her peers, Cyril Figgis, a mild-mannered accountant-turned-agent, Cheryl Tunt, Malory&amp;rsquo;s delusional, psychotic personal assistant and Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Band of Brothers</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/band_of_brothers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/band_of_brothers/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: The miniseries follows Easy Company, an army unit during World War II, from their initial training at Camp Toccoa to the conclusion of the war. The series is based on the book written by the late Stephen E. Ambrose.
Band of Brothers is executive produced by Steven Spielberg and Tom Hanks, the series won 6 Emmy Awards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Battlestar Galactica (2003)</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/battlestar_galactica_2003/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/battlestar_galactica_2003/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: In a distant part of the universe, a civilization of humans live on planets known as the Twelve Colonies. In the past, the Colonies have been at war with a cybernetic race known as the Cylons. 40 years after the first war the Cylons launch a devastating attack on the Colonies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blackadder</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/blackadder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/blackadder/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Through four series and a few specials, Edmund Blackadder and his greasy sidekick Baldrick conjure up cunning plans as Edmund tries to take advantage of desperate times. These situation tragedies had obvious parallels from the Dark Ages to Elizabethan times, the rule of mad George III, and The Great War.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breaking Bad</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/breaking_bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/breaking_bad/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Walter White, a struggling high school chemistry teacher, is diagnosed with advanced lung cancer. He turns to a life of crime, producing and selling methamphetamine accompanied by a former student, Jesse Pinkman, with the aim of securing his family&amp;rsquo;s financial future before he dies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bron/Broen (2011)</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/bron_broen_2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/bron_broen_2011/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: A present-day crime thriller exploring the tensions on the US-Mexico border. When an American judge known for her anti-immigration views is found dead on the bridge connecting El Paso and Juarez, Sonya Cross from El Paso PD must work with her Mexican counterpart from Chihuahua State Police, Marco Ruiz, to catch a serial killer operating on both sides of the border.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buiten de Zone</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/buiten_de_zone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/buiten_de_zone/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: &amp;lsquo;Buiten de Zone&amp;rsquo; is set at a telephone exchange, run by five volunteers, who try to answer the telephone calls from people of their own age. They don&amp;rsquo;t get many calls however, which lets them get carried away by their daydreams about all sorts of important things, like adventure, danger, fear, seduction and love, nostalgia, goodbyes and, of course, eternal life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desperate Housewives</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/desperate_housewives/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/desperate_housewives/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: In the town of Fairview there&amp;rsquo;s a street called Wisteria Lane; a peaceful cul-de-sac with manicured lawns and beautiful houses. It&amp;rsquo;s a place where you know all your neighbors and your neighbors know all about you. It&amp;rsquo;s the perfect suburban fantasy.
But, behind every picket fence there are secrets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discovery Channel Documentaries</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/discovery_channel_documentaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/discovery_channel_documentaries/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Discovery Channel (formerly The Discovery Channel from 1985 to 1995, and often referred to as simply &amp;ldquo;Discovery&amp;rdquo;) is an American basic cable and satellite television channel (which is also delivered via IPTV, terrestrial television and internet television in other parts of the world).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DuckTales</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/ducktales/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/ducktales/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: When Donald Duck decides to join the Navy, he leaves his nephews, Huey, Dewey and Louie, in the care of his cantankerous Uncle Scrooge. He is an eccentric and miserly billionare who loves to literally swim in his money that is held in his corporate headquarters/vault known as the Money Bin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fawlty Towers</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/fawlty_towers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/fawlty_towers/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Hotel owner Basil Fawlty&amp;rsquo;s incompetence, short fuse, and arrogance form a combination that ensures accidents and trouble are never far away.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flesh and Blood</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/flesh_and_blood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/flesh_and_blood/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: A tragicomedy about the everyday life of a butchers family Vangenechten. The business is running fine until the son returns home after a long time. He wants to learn more about the butchers trade and want to take over the butchers shop so it stays in the family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game of Thrones</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/game_of_thrones/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/game_of_thrones/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Seven noble families fight for control of the mythical land of Westeros. Friction between the houses leads to full-scale war. All while a very ancient evil awakens in the farthest north. Amidst the war, a neglected military order of misfits, the Night&amp;rsquo;s Watch, is all that stands between the realms of men and the icy horrors beyond.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hustle</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/hustle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/hustle/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: From the makers of Spooks and acclaimed writer Tony Jordan comes a slick and stylish new drama. An action-packed blend of humour and intrigue, following the fortunes of a gang of expert cons on the loose in London. They are specialists in the way of the grifter and all are keen to liberate cash from the amoral and undeserving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Malcolm in the Middle</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/malcolm_in_the_middle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/malcolm_in_the_middle/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Created and executive-produced by Emmy Award-winning writer Linwood Boomer, this inventive half-hour series is seen through the eyes of Malcolm (Frankie Muniz), a regular high school kid trying to navigate his way through life despite the various obstacles thrown in his way a complete misunderstanding of girls, the constant burden of masterminding plans to get himself and his brothers into or out of trouble, and a miserable job at the Lucky Aide not to mention a severe case of teen angst.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Robot</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/mr._robot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/mr._robot/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Mr. Robot follows Elliot, a young programmer who works as a cyber-security engineer by day and a vigilante hacker by night. Elliot finds himself at a crossroads when the mysterious leader of an underground hacker group recruits him to destroy the corporation he is paid to protect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neveneffecten, Het Beste Van</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/neveneffecten_het_beste_van/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/neveneffecten_het_beste_van/</guid>
      <description>                         Artist Bio: </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Occupied</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/occupied/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/occupied/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: In the near future, Norway is occupied by Russia on behalf of the European Union, due to the fact that the newly elected environmental friendly Norwegian government has stopped the all important oil- and gas-production in the North Sea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quiz me Quick</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/quiz_me_quick/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/quiz_me_quick/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: &amp;ldquo;Quiz Me Quick&amp;rdquo; tells the story of five underdogs, meeting by chance during a quiz in a local pub. They get the idea of taking part in the &amp;ldquo;Superprestige&amp;rdquo;, the most important quiz. The selection procedure turns out to be difficult, requiring more than just knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sherlock</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/sherlock/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/sherlock/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Sherlock Holmes and Dr John Watson&amp;rsquo;s adventures in 21st Century London. A thrilling, funny, fast-paced contemporary reimagining of the Arthur Conan Doyle classic</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Grand Tour (2016)</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/the_grand_tour_2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/the_grand_tour_2016/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: A show about adventure, excitement and friendship&amp;hellip; as long as you accept that the people you call friends are also the ones you find extremely annoying. Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s even a show about cars. Follow Jeremy Clarkson, Richard Hammond and James May on their global adventure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Jetsons</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/the_jetsons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/the_jetsons/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: The Jetsons is an animated sitcom that was produced by Hanna-Barbera. It was Hanna-Barbera’s Space Age counterpart to The Flintstones, a half-hour family sitcom projecting contemporary American culture and lifestyle into another time period. The Jetsons live in a futuristic utopia in the year 2062 of elaborate robotic contraptions, aliens, holograms, and whimsical inventions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Pacific</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/the_pacific/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/the_pacific/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: A 10-part mini-series from the creators of &amp;ldquo;Band of Brothers&amp;rdquo;, The Pacific focuses on the United States Marine Corps&amp;rsquo; actions in the Pacific Theater of Operations within the wider Pacific War. Whereas Band of Brothers followed one Army infantry company through the European Theater, The Pacific follows three Marines (Eugene Sledge, Robert Leckie and John Basilone) in separate combat actions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Walking Dead</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/the_walking_dead/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/the_walking_dead/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: The series centers on sheriff&amp;rsquo;s deputy Rick Grimes, who wakes up from a coma to discover the apocalypse. He becomes the leader of a group of survivors from the Atlanta, Georgia region as they attempt to sustain themselves and protect themselves not only against attacks by walkers but by other groups of survivors willing to assure their longevity by any means necessary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thunderbirds</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/thunderbirds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/thunderbirds/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Thunderbirds are Go!! The year is 2065, and a secret organization called International Rescue has been created by multi-millionaire Jeff Tracy. The team consists of his five sons and brilliant engineer Brains. From their headquarters on Tracy Island somewhere in the South Pacific, International Rescue helps people in danger all over the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top Gear</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/top_gear/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/top_gear/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: This fast-paced and stunt-filled motor show tests whether cars, both mundane and extraordinary, live up to their manufacturers&amp;rsquo; claims. The long-running show travels to locations around the world, performing extreme stunts and challenges to see what the featured cars are capable of doing. Celebrity guests appear on some episodes to help test the vehicles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vaneigens</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/vaneigens/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/vaneigens/</guid>
      <description>                         Artist Bio: </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Westworld</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/westworld/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/westworld/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Westworld is a dark odyssey about the dawn of artificial consciousness and the evolution of sin. Set at the intersection of the near future and the reimagined past, it explores a world in which every human appetite, no matter how noble or depraved, can be indulged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zorro (1990)</title>
      <link>/tv_shows/zorro_1990/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tv_shows/zorro_1990/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Set in Spanish California, this often-refilmed story chronicles the adventures of Don Diego de la Vega, a young nobleman who lives a double live as El Zorro (&amp;lsquo;the Fox&amp;rsquo;), protector of the people of the Pueblo de Los Angeles during the early 1800s. Hiding behind the mannerisms of a bookish fop, Diego keeps his second identity hidden from everyone but his servant, Felipe.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>