<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music on First-Gear.be</title>
    <link>/music/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Music on First-Gear.be</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AC/DC</title>
      <link>/music/ac_dc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/ac_dc/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: AC/DC is an Australian rock band formed in Sydney, New South Wales, Australia in December 1973 by Angus and Malcolm Young. Their albums have sold in colossal numbers; the total is now estimated at well over 200 million copies worldwide, with the 1980 album Back In Black selling over 21 million in the US alone and 40+ million worldwide, making it, according to statistics, one of the best selling albums in the world, outsold only by Michael Jackson&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Thriller&amp;rsquo;, and tied with Pink Floyd&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Dark Side of the Moon&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Absolute Power Metal</title>
      <link>/music/absolute_power_metal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/absolute_power_metal/</guid>
      <description>                         Artist Bio: No Summary Found For: Absolute Power Metal
Albums:  Album: The Definitive Collection Vol. 1
 Album: The Definitive Collection Vol. 2
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Absynthe Minded</title>
      <link>/music/absynthe_minded/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/absynthe_minded/</guid>
      <description>                         Artist Bio: The Belgian alternative rock outfit Absynthe Minded is heavily influenced by thirties jazz, soul, Merseyside pop, balkan and gypsy music.
Albums:  Album: Absynthe Minded
 Album: Acquired Taste
 Album: New Day
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ace of Base</title>
      <link>/music/ace_of_base/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/ace_of_base/</guid>
      <description>                         Artist Bio: Swedish pop group Ace of Base was formed in Göteborg, Sweden in 1990.
Albums:  Album: Singles of the 90s  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adele</title>
      <link>/music/adele/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/adele/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Adele Laurie Blue Adkins, (born 5 May 1988), is a multiple Grammy Award-Winning English singer-songwriter from Enfield, North London. Her debut album, 19, was released in January 2008 and entered the UK album chart at #1. The album has since received four-times Platinum certification in the UK and has sold 5,500,000 copies worldwide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Admiral Freebee</title>
      <link>/music/admiral_freebee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/admiral_freebee/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: &amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;each one gets the honey and each one gets the knife, but fools like us always survive&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; * A non-conforming magazine gave its music journalists a daunting task a couple of years ago, of having to sum up the new and upcoming records in just 1 single word.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alan Parsons Project</title>
      <link>/music/alan_parsons_project/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/alan_parsons_project/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: The Alan Parsons Project was a British rock group active from 1975 until 1990, founded by Alan Parsons and Eric Woolfson both from London, England. The group is based on a number of regular group members such as Stuart Elliot and Ian Bairnson, complemented with varying lead vocals such as Colin Blunstone (the Zombies), Chris Rainbow and Gary Brooker (Procol Harum).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alanis Morissette</title>
      <link>/music/alanis_morissette/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/alanis_morissette/</guid>
      <description>                         Artist Bio: Alanis Nadine Morissette (born June 1, 1974) is a seven time Grammy Award-winning Canadian singer-songwriter and occasional actress. She is the best-selling female rock artist of all time.
Albums:  Album: The Collection  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alestorm</title>
      <link>/music/alestorm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/alestorm/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Alestorm is a folk metal band from Perth, Scotland. Their music is characterized by a pirate theme, and as a result have been dubbed a pirate metal band on a popular heavy metal related website. They refer to their genre as &amp;ldquo;True Scottish Pirate Metal&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amy MacDonald</title>
      <link>/music/amy_macdonald/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/amy_macdonald/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Amy Macdonald (born 25 August 1987 in Bishopbriggs, East Dunbartonshire) is a Scottish recording artist. Macdonald rose to fame in 2007 with her debut album, This Is the Life (2007) and its fourth single, &amp;ldquo;This Is the Life&amp;rdquo;. The single charted at number one in six countries, while reaching the top ten in another eleven countries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angra</title>
      <link>/music/angra/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/angra/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Angra are a progressive power metal formation from São Paulo, Brazil. Formed in 1991, with Andre Matos (vocals), Luís Mariutti (bass), Marcos Antunes (drums), André Linhares (guitar) and Rafael Bittencourt (guitar). In 1992, Linhares was replaced by André Hernandes, later replaced by Kiko Loureiro.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anouk</title>
      <link>/music/anouk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/anouk/</guid>
      <description>                         Artist Bio: Anouk (Anouk Teeuwe, born April 8th, 1975 in Den Haag, Netherlands), is a multi platinum selling and multi award winning Dutch singer.
Albums:  Album: Hotel New York  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Armin van Buuren</title>
      <link>/music/armin_van_buuren/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/armin_van_buuren/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Armin van Buuren (born Armin Jozef Jacobus Daniël van Buuren, December 25, 1976) is a trance (mostly progressive trance and uplifting trance) music producer and DJ from the Netherlands. His musical career started in 1995.
Albums:  Album: 76
 Album: Imagine
 Album: Mirage</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avantasia</title>
      <link>/music/avantasia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/avantasia/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Avantasia, from Germany, is the side-project of Edguy singer Tobias Sammet, founded in 1999. Two concept albums were released (The Metal Opera, The Metal Opera Pt. II), their structures similar to that of an opera. Both can be classified as Power Metal and/or Symphonic Metal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Axelle Red</title>
      <link>/music/axelle_red/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/axelle_red/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Axelle Red was born Fabienne Demal in Hasselt, Flanders, Belgium, on February 15, 1968. She is a singer-songwriter. Despite being Flemish, she chose to write and perform songs in the French language. She has achieved great critical success in both Belgium and France. Her musical style varies from jazz to piano ballads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bart Peeters</title>
      <link>/music/bart_peeters/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/bart_peeters/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Bart Peeters is a Belgian (Flemish) singer from Antwerp, drummer, television presenter and actor. He gained fame with The Radios wich started in 1989 but nowadays he is a solo artist. In 2004 he made his first solo album called Het plaatje van Bart Peeters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beirut</title>
      <link>/music/beirut/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/beirut/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Beirut is an American indie-rock and world music band which was originally the solo musical project of Zach Condon (born Zachary Francis Condon in Santa Fe, New Mexico) and later expanded into a band. The band&amp;rsquo;s first performances were in New York, in May 2006, to support the release of their debut album, Gulag Orkestar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Birdy</title>
      <link>/music/birdy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/birdy/</guid>
      <description>                         Artist Bio: Birdy is a name of at least four artists: 1. A British singer songwriter 2. A French electronic musician 3. A German electronic musician 4. An American acoustic group
Albums:  Album: Birdy  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Black Sabbath</title>
      <link>/music/black_sabbath/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/black_sabbath/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Black Sabbath was an English heavy metal band that formed in 1968 in Birmingham, West Midlands, England, United Kingdom and disbanded in 2017, originally comprising Ozzy Osbourne (vocals), Tony Iommi (guitar), Geezer Butler (bass), and Bill Ward (drums). In the early 70s, they were the first to pair heavily distorted, sonically dissonant blues rock at slow speeds with lyrics about drugs, mental pain and abominations of war, thus giving birth to generations of metal bands that followed in their wake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blink-182</title>
      <link>/music/blink-182/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/blink-182/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Blink-182 is an American rock band formed in Poway, a suburb of San Diego, California in 1992. The band currently consists of bassist and vocalist Mark Hoppus, drummer Travis Barker, and guitarist and vocalist Matt Skiba. Blink-182 is considered a key group in the development of pop punk; the band&amp;rsquo;s combination of pop melodies with fast-paced punk rock featured a more radio-friendly accessibility than prior bands.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blondie</title>
      <link>/music/blondie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/blondie/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Blondie is an American rock band founded in New York City in 1974 by singer-songwriter Deborah Harry and guitarist Chris Stein. The band was a pioneer in the early American new wave and punk scenes of the mid-70s, developing their sound in famous NYC clubs such as CBGBs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buscemi</title>
      <link>/music/buscemi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/buscemi/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Since 1996, Dirk Swartenbroekx (Lommel, Belgium) is making &amp;ldquo;warm&amp;rdquo; records under the name of Buscemi. He called himself after Steve Buscemi, one of his favorite actors. His style is deep and difficult to categorise: nu bossa, nu lounge, house, brazilian grooves, afrobeat, drum &amp;lsquo;n bass&amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;Dancemusic with a latin feel&amp;rdquo; is maybe the best description of the sound of Buscemi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carl Orff</title>
      <link>/music/carl_orff/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/carl_orff/</guid>
      <description>                         Artist Bio: Carl Orff (10th July 1895–29th March 1982) was a German composer, most famous for his Carmina Burana (1937), and an important and influential music educator.
Albums:  Album: Orff: Carmina Burana  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cirque du Soleil</title>
      <link>/music/cirque_du_soleil/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/cirque_du_soleil/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Cirque du Soleil (French for &amp;ldquo;Circus of the Sun&amp;rdquo;) is an entertainment empire based in Montréal, Quebec, Canada and founded in Quebec in 1984 by two former street performers, Guy Laliberté and Daniel Gauthier. It was an answer to a call by Commissariat général aux célébrations 1534-1984 of the Quebec Government for the 450th anniversary celebration of the discovery of Canada by French explorer Jacques Cartier (b 1491-d 1557).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coldplay</title>
      <link>/music/coldplay/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/coldplay/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Coldplay is a British alternative rock band, formed in London, United Kingdom in 1997. The band comprises vocalist and pianist Chris Martin, lead guitarist Jonny Buckland – who met each other in September 1996 at Ramsay Hall (halls of residence) at University College London - bassist Guy Berryman and drummer Will Champion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daan</title>
      <link>/music/daan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/daan/</guid>
      <description>                         Artist Bio: Daan is a dutch DJ. Read more on Last.fm. User-contributed text is available under the Creative Commons By-SA License; additional terms may apply
Albums:  Album: Bridge Burner
 Album: Manhay
 Album: Victory
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Bowie</title>
      <link>/music/david_bowie/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/david_bowie/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: David Bowie (b. David Robert Jones on 8th January 1947 in Brixton, London, UK, d. 10th January 2016 in New York, USA) was an English rock singer, songwriter, musician, and actor. Active during six decades of popular music and frequently reinventing his music and image, Bowie is widely regarded as an innovator, particularly for his work in the 1970s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deep Purple</title>
      <link>/music/deep_purple/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/deep_purple/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Deep Purple is an English hard rock band that formed in Hertfordshire in 1968. Together with groups such as Black Sabbath and Led Zeppelin, they&amp;rsquo;re considered as heavy metal pioneers. Especially influential to later metal bands were Ian Gillan&amp;rsquo;s powerful screams and Ritchie Blackmore&amp;rsquo;s virtuoso solos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duran Duran</title>
      <link>/music/duran_duran/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/duran_duran/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Duran Duran (named after a character in Roger Vadim&amp;rsquo;s sci-fi classic, Barbarella) is an electronic pop rock band that was part of the New Wave movement of the 80s and 90s. Created by Nick Rhodes (keyboards) and John Taylor (bass) in Birmingham, England in 1978, it later add took in Roger Taylor (drums), Andy Taylor (guitar), and Simon Le Bon (lead vocals).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editors</title>
      <link>/music/editors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/editors/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: 1) Editors are a British indie rock/post-punk revival band from Birmingham, England, formed by Tom Smith (vocals, guitar, keyboards), Russell Leetch (bass) Ed Lay (drums) and Chris Urbanowicz (guitar) who met while studying at Staffordshire University, in Stafford, England, United Kingdom during 2002. After Chris&amp;rsquo; departure in 2012 , Justin Lockey and Elliott Williams joined the band for their live gigs and participated in the recording of the fourth album.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ellie Goulding</title>
      <link>/music/ellie_goulding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/ellie_goulding/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Ellie Goulding (born Elena Jane Goulding, 30 December 1986 in Hereford, England) is an English singer-songwriter. Having caught the public&amp;rsquo;s attention in 2010 with her singles &amp;ldquo;Starry Eyed&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Guns and Horses,&amp;rdquo; British vocalist Ellie Goulding quickly rose to the top of the charts with her infectious electronic pop sound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ennio Morricone</title>
      <link>/music/ennio_morricone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/ennio_morricone/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Ennio Morricone, Grand Officer OMRI (born 10 November 1928) is an Italian composer, orchestrator, conductor, and former trumpet player. He composes a wide range of music styles, making him one of the most versatile, experimental and influential composers of all time, working in any medium.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faithless</title>
      <link>/music/faithless/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/faithless/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Formed in 1995 by Sister Bliss, Faithless was a London, England, United Kingdom-based group of musicians whose music is described by one of their band members as a cross between trip-hop and techno. The four original members of Faithless were vocalist/rapper Maxi Jazz, keyboardist/producer Sister Bliss, instrumentalist/vocalist Jamie Catto and keyboardist/producer Rollo Armstrong.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fakear</title>
      <link>/music/fakear/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/fakear/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Fakear is Théo Le Vigoreux - an uncannily suitable name for a young producer whose energy is seemingly limitless. At 24 years old, Fakear has already taken his globally-tuned dance music across the world, playing shows from London to Tokyo, supporting Bonobo and selling out Paris’ prestigious Olympia in 2015.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fixkes</title>
      <link>/music/fixkes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/fixkes/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Fixkes are six fellows from Stabroek, a village north of Antwerp, Belgium. Sam Valkenborgh, his brother Jan Valkenborgh, Peter Deckers, Johan Pauwels, Bart Palmers and Joris Van den Broeck combine since 2005 acoustic pop and rap in the local Dutch dialect. Fans of Jack Johnson, Everlast, G.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fleetwood Mac</title>
      <link>/music/fleetwood_mac/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/fleetwood_mac/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Fleetwood Mac is a British and American blues band formed in 1967. From the band&amp;rsquo;s inception through the end of 1974, no incarnation of Fleetwood Mac lasted longer than two years, but all featured core members Mick Fleetwood and John McVie. Their two most successful periods have been during the late 60s British blues boom, when they were led by guitarist/singer-songwriter Peter Green, and from 1975 to 1987, when they went a pop-oriented direction with musicians Christine McVie, Lindsey Buckingham, and Stevie Nicks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foreigner</title>
      <link>/music/foreigner/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/foreigner/</guid>
      <description>                         Artist Bio: Foreigner is a British-American rock band, originally formed in 1976 by the veteran English musician Mick Jones and fellow Briton and ex-King Crimson member Ian McDonald along with American vocalist Lou Gramm.
Albums:  Album: The Very Best of Foreigner  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gabriel Rios</title>
      <link>/music/gabriel_rios/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/gabriel_rios/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Born in 1978 in Puerto Rico, Gabriel Rios soon chose a path which few from his kin before him did. A blonde angel whispered that he should follow her lead. Young Gabriel kicked his heels and travelled through turbulent clouds, ending up in a city that was not his, but which he embraced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golden Earring</title>
      <link>/music/golden_earring/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/golden_earring/</guid>
      <description>                         Artist Bio: Golden Earring is the best known and internationally most succesful rock band to come out of the Netherlands.
Albums:  Album: Golden Earring  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Day</title>
      <link>/music/green_day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/green_day/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Green Day is an American punk rock band formed in 1986 by lead vocalist and guitarist Billie Joe Armstrong and bassist Mike Dirnt. For much of the band&amp;rsquo;s career, they have been a trio with drummer Tré Cool, who replaced John Kiffmeyer in 1990 prior to the recording of the band&amp;rsquo;s second studio album, Kerplunk (1991).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hooverphonic</title>
      <link>/music/hooverphonic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/hooverphonic/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Hooverphonic is a Belgian rock/pop group formed in 1995. Though initially placed in the trip-hop genre, they quickly expanded their sound to the point where they could no longer be classified so easily. The band originally called themselves Hoover but later changed their name to Hooverphonic due to other groups using the Hoover name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K&#39;s Choice</title>
      <link>/music/ks_choice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/ks_choice/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: K&amp;rsquo;s Choice is a Belgian rock band from Antwerp. The band centers on siblings Sarah Bettens (lead vocals, guitar) and Gert Bettens (guitar, keyboard, vocals). They are joined by Eric Grossman (bass), Jan van Sichem Jr. (guitar) and Koen Liekens (drums).
Albums:  Album: Allmost Happy</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KISS</title>
      <link>/music/kiss/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/kiss/</guid>
      <description>                         Artist Bio: There are three groups of artists with this name:
Albums:  Album: KISS Alive 35: Oslo  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Katie Melua</title>
      <link>/music/katie_melua/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/katie_melua/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Ketevan “Katie” Melua (Georgian: ქეთევან “ქეთი” მელუა, surname pronounced IPA: /ˈmeluˌɑː/; born 16 September 1984) is a British-Georgian singer-songwriter and musician. She was born in the Georgian S.S.R., but moved to Northern Ireland at the age of eight and then relocated to England at the age of 14.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kooks</title>
      <link>/music/kooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/kooks/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: British indie rock band - formed in Brighton, England, United Kingdom in 2004. The band currently consists of Luke Pritchard (vocals, guitar), Hugh Harris (guitar), Peter Denton (bass) and Nick Millard (drums). Nick is currently filling in for Paul Garred due to a recent arm injury.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linkin Park</title>
      <link>/music/linkin_park/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/linkin_park/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Linkin Park is an American band from Agoura Hills, California. Formed in 1996, the band rose to international fame with their debut album, Hybrid Theory, which was certified Diamond by the RIAA in 2005 and multi-platinum in several other countries. Linkin Park has released seven studio albums (2000&amp;rsquo;s Hybrid Theory, 2003&amp;rsquo;s Meteora, 2007&amp;rsquo;s Minutes to Midnight, 2010&amp;rsquo;s A Thousand Suns, 2012&amp;rsquo;s Living Things, 2014&amp;rsquo;s The Hunting Party, and 2017&amp;rsquo;s One More Light).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manau</title>
      <link>/music/manau/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/manau/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Manau is a Hip Hop group from France formed in 1998, known for their fusing of traditional Celtic melodies with modern rap beats. It was initially composed of Martial Tricoche, Cédric Soubiron, and R.V. (Hervé) Lardic until R.V.&amp;rsquo;s departure and replacement by Gregor Gandon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mika</title>
      <link>/music/mika/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/mika/</guid>
      <description>                         Artist Bio: There are multiple bands/artists under the name Mika.
Albums:  Album: Life in Cartoon Motion  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Milk Inc</title>
      <link>/music/milk_inc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/milk_inc/</guid>
      <description>                         Artist Bio: No Summary Found For: Milk Inc
Albums:  Album: Milk Inc Live - Supersized 2  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nirvana</title>
      <link>/music/nirvana/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/nirvana/</guid>
      <description>                         Artist Bio: There are multiple artists tracked as &amp;ldquo;Nirvana&amp;rdquo; on Last.fm. Following are six, listed in order of prominence:
Albums:  Album: Bleach
 Album: In Utero
 Album: Nevermind
 Album: [non-album tracks]
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paramore</title>
      <link>/music/paramore/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/paramore/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Paramore is an American Grammy-award winning rock band formed in Franklin, Tennessee, United States in 2004. The band currently consists of Hayley Williams (vocals), Taylor York (guitar) and Zac Farro (drums). They have released five studio albums: All We Know Is Falling (2005), RIOT!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Praga Khan</title>
      <link>/music/praga_khan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/praga_khan/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Praga Khan (aka Maurice Joseph Francois Engelen) is an early Techno musician from Belgium. His Belgian New Beat style stems back to the late 80s when Techno came out of the Belgian underground. The Belgian studio wizard is responsible for some of the most important and most recognized rave tracks of the late 80s and early 90s, under his own name and several of his band names (Lords of Acid, Digital Orgasm, Channel X).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shaman</title>
      <link>/music/shaman/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/shaman/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: There are at least nine artists known under this name:
 Finnish Folk Metal band (later changed their name to Korpiklaani), Brazilian Power Metal band (known as Shaaman, but has since reformed as Shaman), German Progressive Trance Producer, Russian rapper and beatmaker from group “Район Моей Мечты”, South Korean brutal death metal band, US Folk group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sigur Rós</title>
      <link>/music/sigur_r%C3%B3s/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/sigur_r%C3%B3s/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Sigur Rós are an Icelandic post-rock band. The name is derived from the name of lead vocalist Jónsi Birgisson&amp;rsquo;s little sister, Sigurrós. They hail from the same creative and vibrant Icelandic music scene as múm and Amiina. They released their first ever foray into film-making with their tour documentary, Heima in late 2007.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snow Patrol</title>
      <link>/music/snow_patrol/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/snow_patrol/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Snow Patrol are an alternative rock band that formed in Dundee, Scotland, United Kingdom in 1994 and currently based in Bangor, Northern Ireland, where most of the band members are from. They consist of Gary Lightbody (vocals, guitar), Nathan Connolly (guitar, vocals), Paul Wilson (bass), Tom Simpson (keyboards) and Jonny Quinn (drums).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soulsister</title>
      <link>/music/soulsister/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/soulsister/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Soulsister is a Belgian music band consisting of musicians Jan Leyers and Paul Michiels. SoulSister (also known as the Soul Sisters and Leyers, Michiels, and SoulSister) ran from 1986 until 1995 and performed a mix of pop and soul. They will reunite at The Night of the Proms in 2007.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start To Run</title>
      <link>/music/start_to_run/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/start_to_run/</guid>
      <description>                         Artist Bio: No Summary Found For: Start To Run
Albums:  Album: Start To Run (5-10)
 Album: Stat To Run
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stash</title>
      <link>/music/stash/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/stash/</guid>
      <description>                         Artist Bio: There are at least two artists under this name&amp;hellip;.
Albums:  Album: Rock &amp;lsquo;n&amp;rsquo; Roll Show  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tears for Fears</title>
      <link>/music/tears_for_fears/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/tears_for_fears/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Tears for Fears, named after a phrase found in Arthur Janov&amp;rsquo;s book Prisoners of Pain, is a British pop/rock outfit formed in 1981 in Bath, England. Founder members Roland Orzabal and Curt Smith had been friends since their early teens and had already been in the shortlived ska band Graduate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Beach Boys</title>
      <link>/music/the_beach_boys/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/the_beach_boys/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: The Beach Boys are an iconic American rock band, frequently cited as one of the most influential and commercially successful groups in the history of popular music due to their intricate vocal harmonies, studio experiments, and novel approaches to pop songwriting. Rooted in doo-wop and rock and roll, their early string of vocal surf hits defined the &amp;lsquo;60s California Sound.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Bravery</title>
      <link>/music/the_bravery/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/the_bravery/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: The Bravery is an alternative rock band with electronic influences, formed in New York City in 2003. Their musical style has been compared to The Strokes, New Order and The Killers, amongst others. They are best known for three songs - 2005&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;An Honest Mistake&amp;rdquo;, 2007&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Time Won&amp;rsquo;t Let Me Go&amp;rdquo; and 2008&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Believe&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Corrs</title>
      <link>/music/the_corrs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/the_corrs/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: The Corrs are a folk pop band from Dundalk, Ireland, consisting of three sisters and one brother from the Corr family, who rose to prominence in the late 1990s and have since sold more than 55 million albums worldwide. The band consists of siblings Jim Corr (keyboard, guitar, backing vocals, born July 31, 1964), Sharon Corr (violin, backing vocals, born March 24, 1970), Caroline Corr (drums, bodhran, piano, backing vocals, born March 17, 1973) and Andrea Corr (lead vocals, tin whistle, born May 17, 1974).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cranberries</title>
      <link>/music/the_cranberries/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/the_cranberries/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: The Cranberries is an alternative rock band from Limerick, Ireland that formed in 1989 and rose to mainstream popularity in the early 1990&amp;rsquo;s. The band consists of Dolores O&amp;rsquo;Riordan (vocals, keyboards, guitars), Noel Hogan (guitars, vocals, also a member of Mono Band), Mike Hogan (bass, vocals), and Fergal Lawler (drums, percussion, also a member of The Low Network).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fray</title>
      <link>/music/the_fray/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/the_fray/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: From the sleepy sprawl of America&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Mile-High City&amp;rsquo;, Denver, Colorado, United States, comes The Fray, a foursome whose melodic piano rock songs and soaring vocals resonate with sprawling tapestries and tales of hopefulness and heartache. Formed in 2002 by Isaac Slade (vocals, piano) and Joe King (guitar, vocals), The Fray earned a loyal grassroots following through impressive area gigs and the support of local radio, which led a listener-driven campaign to get the band a record contract.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Prodigy</title>
      <link>/music/the_prodigy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/the_prodigy/</guid>
      <description>                         Artist Bio: The Prodigy are a Braintree, Essex, UK, electronic music group (aka Prodigy), formed by Liam Howlett (composition, keyboards), in 1990. They have sold over 20 million records worldwide, which is almost unequalled in dance music history.
Albums:  Album: Their Law: The Singles 1990&amp;frasl;2  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Rolling Stones</title>
      <link>/music/the_rolling_stones/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/the_rolling_stones/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: The Rolling Stones are an English rock group that formed in London in 1962. First popular in Europe, they quickly became successful in North America during the &amp;ldquo;British Invasion&amp;rdquo; of the mid-60s. Since then, their worldwide sales are estimated at more than 200 million albums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Script</title>
      <link>/music/the_script/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/the_script/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: The Script are a pop rock band which formed in 2001 in Dublin, Ireland. The band consists of Danny O&amp;rsquo;Donoghue (vocals), Mark Sheehan (guitar) and Glen Power (drums).
Albums:  Album: No Sound Without Silence
 Album: Science &amp;amp; Faith
 Album: [Unknown Album]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Smashing Pumpkins</title>
      <link>/music/the_smashing_pumpkins/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/the_smashing_pumpkins/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: The Smashing Pumpkins are an alternative rock band, formed in Chicago, Illinois, USA, in 1988. Billy Corgan and James Iha met in a record store, and began performing in local nightclubs with their bassist, D&amp;rsquo;arcy Wretzky, using a drum machine. Playing with a drum machine frustrated both the band and their audience, and so Chicago jazz drummer Jimmy Chamberlin was hired soon afterwards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Who</title>
      <link>/music/the_who/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/the_who/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: The Who are an English rock band formed in 1964. Their classic line-up consisted of lead singer Roger Daltrey, guitarist and singer Pete Townshend, bass guitarist John Entwistle, and drummer Keith Moon. They are considered one of the most influential rock bands of the 20th century, selling over 100 million records worldwide and holding a reputation for their live shows and studio work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tori Amos</title>
      <link>/music/tori_amos/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/tori_amos/</guid>
      <description>                         Artist Bio: Tori Amos (born Myra Ellen Amos on 22 August 1963 in Newton, North Carolina, United States) is an American pianist and singer-songwriter.
Albums:  Album: Little Earthquakes  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>U2</title>
      <link>/music/u2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/u2/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: U2 are an Irish rock band from Dublin formed in 1976. The group consists of Bono (lead vocals and rhythm guitar), the Edge (lead guitar, keyboards, and backing vocals), Adam Clayton (bass guitar), and Larry Mullen Jr. (drums and percussion). Initially rooted in post-punk, U2&amp;rsquo;s musical style evolved throughout their career, yet has maintained an anthemic sound built on Bono&amp;rsquo;s expressive vocals and the Edge&amp;rsquo;s effects-based guitar textures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uriah Heep</title>
      <link>/music/uriah_heep/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/uriah_heep/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Uriah Heep is a British rock band, officially formed in 1969 in London, England, when record producer Gerry Bron invited keyboardist Ken Hensley (previously a member of The Gods and Toe Fat) to join Spice, members of whom included soon-to-become Heep stalwarts David Byron (vocals) and Mick Box (guitar).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Games Live</title>
      <link>/music/video_games_live/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/video_games_live/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Created by two industry leading video game composers Tommy Tallarico and Jack Wall, Video Games Live™ (produced under their company Mystical Stone Entertainment, LLC) is the front runner in the field of live game music performance. Video Games Live™ is an immersive concert event celebration featuring music from the biggest video games of all time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weezer</title>
      <link>/music/weezer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/weezer/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Weezer is an American rock band. Formed in 1992, they have released 11 full length albums, 1 covers album, six EPs, and a DVD. Their latest album, titled &amp;lsquo;Weezer (Teal Album)&amp;rsquo;, came out on January 23rd, 2019. They&amp;rsquo;ve sold over nine million records in the United States to date.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You Me At Six</title>
      <link>/music/you_me_at_six/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/you_me_at_six/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: You Me At Six are a 5-piece pop punk band from Weybridge, Surrey who formed in 2005. The five piece played locally until early 2007 when spring support slots with Saosin at Leeds Cockpit (03.05.07) and later Paramore at the Colchester Arts Centre (10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zornik</title>
      <link>/music/zornik/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/zornik/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: Zornik is a Belgian rock band, from Zonhoven, which gained a fair amount of mainstream attention. It was formed in 1999 by Koen Buyse (singer and guitarist), Marijn Horemans (drums) and Kristof Vanduren (bass). In 2003, Kristof decided to leave the band. For the summer festival shows, he was replaced by Bas Remans (Millionaire) who also joined the band in the studio for the recordings of the second album.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dEUS</title>
      <link>/music/deus/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/deus/</guid>
      <description>Artist Bio: dEUS is an alternative/experimental rock band based and formed in Antwerp, Belgium. dEUS’s lineup has changed frequently, with only singer and guitarist Tom Barman and multi-instrumentalist Klaas Janszoons remaining from the original setting. The other current members are guitarist and vocalist Mauro Pawlowski, bassist Alan Gevaert and drummer Stephane Misseghers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>